[gentle music]
Don't follow accounts like this online.
Let me tell you why.
That's an Aventador SVJ.
To get a decent one, mate,
that's like a million dollars.
That's in Australian.
But it's like a million dollars.
When you earn 100K a month,
you're not there. I'll explain.
You have these months where you make over
six figures a month, and you think to
yourself, "Oh my god,
I'm going to get an SVJ."
But you're really not.
First of all, ads. Everyone's like,
"Look at my rev." Brother,
40 to 45% of that
you're spending in ads. So out of
that 100K you made, 45 of it
gone straight to Meta.
So you're left with, like, 60. Sweet.
Now you've got to pay your staff.
Because if you are making 100K a month,
and
you're doing it on your own,
you're a fucking idiot because you can't
service that
amount of business. But
if you're doing it the smart way,
you've probably got four
to 10 members of staff. Now,
if you're lucky, you're down to,
let's say, 30, 20K.
The government's taking half. Yeah,
the government's taking half.
You're left with, like, 10. Maybe 15.
At that, you need a nice house.
These fuckers need feeding.
The truth and reality of it
is I've literally had months where I've
done 100K,
I've not even taken a dividend.
There's not even been enough left for me
at the end
of it. But I could sit here and go, "Oh,
100K a month. Oh, SVJ. Oh, Miami.
Oh." It's not the reality of running a
business.
Revenue and profit
are two very different things.
But these videos are there for young kids
to get very excited.
And you can get a Huracán.
It's a quarter of the price,
and it's just as much fun.
You won't even know the difference.
You and I are not good enough at driving
to notice the difference between those
cars.
"But the Aventador SVJ will hold its
money."
Shut up